Matt Lim

San Francisco, California, US | +1 (925) 639-4567 | mattlim33@gmail.com mattlim.me | github.com/arcticmatt | linkedin.com/in/itsmlim

Software Engineer and Founder

I've been working as a software engineer for the last 6 years across full stack web development, systems engineering, and product infra. My strength is building polished and scalable products, often from zero to one. Outside of "work-work," I love building side projects, some of which are listed below (see my website for the rest).

Work Experience

Co-Founder and CTO, Formfunction

Jun 2021 - Jun 2023

- Raised a \$4.7M seed round from firms including Variant Fund and Pear VC.
- Built an NFT marketplace where creators could sell their digital art. Used React + Relay on the frontend, Express.js + GraphQL + Postgres on the backend, and Rust for the Solana programs. Processed \$5 million in volume and made over \$200,000 in revenue in the first year.
- Hired and led a team of 4 engineers.

Senior Software Engineer, Meta/Facebook

Sep 2017 - Jun 2021

- Full stack lead for a team in New Product Experimentation focused on social activism. Built a web app from zero to one that let people share and discover causes they care about, using React and GraphQL.
- AR/VR systems engineer. Designed and implemented a communication protocol that worked over Bluetooth,
 TCP, and STP. It was written in C++ and used for prototyping a number of new headsets.
- Product infra engineer in Integrity, led team of 4. Built a platformized way for developers to enable reps to
 <u>customize their experiences</u> (e.g. blurring graphic images) using React and GraphQL. Led migration of millions
 of actions per day (e.g. "delete this content") from Haskell to a new framework written in Hack.

Projects

Harken 2023

- Built Harken, a spaced repetition flashcard app that's a better version of Anki, using React/GraphQL/Express.
- Built the <u>Harken Chrome extension</u>, which lets you quiz yourself on content from any article on the internet by using GPT-4 to generate questions with a single click.

Minymon 2021

- Minymons are pets that live on your website and can answer common questions, interact with your visitors, and build your brand. Built with React, GraphQL, and Express.
- Was the #4 product of the day on Product Hunt and has generated \$3,000 in revenue.

Psychedelics Anonymous

2021

• Developed and deployed four ERC-721 smart contracts for the Psychedelics Anonymous NFT project. The four collections sold out in ~1 week and generated \$10 million in revenue.

See <u>mattlim.me</u> for more of my projects.

Skills

Programming Languages: (Expert) JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS, (Experienced) Python, (Familiar) C++ **Technologies**: (Expert) React, GraphQL, Relay, Express.js (Experienced) Next.js, Postgres, Firebase

Education

California Institute of Technology

Jun 2013 – Jun 2017

- B.S in Computer Science, Minor in English
- 4.0 GPA
- TA for EE150, CS156a, CS122, CS156b